https://mindbluff.com/privacy.htm

Privacy Statement for
Mind Bluff
Mind Bluff
has created this privacy
statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.
The following discloses the information gathering and
dissemination practices for this Web site:
Mind Bluff
Information Automatically Logged
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site.
This information is not used for any other purpose.
Cookies
Our Site uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. The cookies are not used for any other purpose.
Advertisers
We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies.
While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are
collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information.
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.
Personal Information
This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally
identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted.
Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal
information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.
External Links
This site contains links to other sites.
Mind Bluff
is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can
contact us.
